Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
- Series VIII. Pamphlets
  - The Tariff. Speech of Hon. Roger Q. Mills Of Texas...April 17, 1888, 1888; 6477.PA0438; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Tariff Question- A Plea For New England. Speech...April 30, 1888, 1888; 6477.PA0439; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Surplus And the Tariff. Speech Of Hon. S.S. Cox...May 17, 1888, 1888; 6477.PA0440; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Mills Bill - Tariff Legislation. Speech Of Hon. William McKinley Jr...May 18, 1888; 6477.PA0441; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - What's Your Opinion? (Anti-McHugh), ca. 1976; 6477.PA0442; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Harter, Bill
  - Matt McHugh Has Earned Our Support, 1976; 6477.PA0443; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Labor's Candidate For Congress 27th District, ca. 1976; 6477.PA0444; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - We Need An Honest, Effective Congressman...And We've Got One, ca. 1976; 6477.PA0445; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Matt McHugh, 1976; 6477.PA0446; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The 200 Times...McHugh For Congress (No's. 1, 4, 5, 6 August-October 1976), 1976; 6477.PA0447; Items: 4 (Box 11)
  - There Are Some Congressmen Who Work For Special Interest Groups, ca. 1976; 6477.PA0448; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - There Are A Few Congressmen You Can Always Count On, 1976; 6477.PA0449; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Pat Moynihan Speaks Out For New York, 1976; 6477.PA0450; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Where Do Pat Moynihan And James Buckley Stand On the Issues?, ca. 1976; 6477.PA0451; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - We Need Legislators Not Politicians Doug Auer For Assembly, ca. 1976; 6477.PA0452; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Auer, Douglas
  - Assemblyman Gary Lee, ca. 1976; 6477.PA0453; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - He's Making Us Proud Again, ca. 1976; 6477.PA0454; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - The Dirty Dozen Campaign (Letter and "Wanted" Folder), ca. 1976; 6477.PA0455; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Udall '76 New York (Campaign Letter), 1976; 6477.PA0456; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Plains Baptist Church (Program January 9, 1977), 1977; 6477.PA0457; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Carter Jimmy
  - Jimmy Carter Presidential Campaign (Policy Statements and Speeches), 1976; 6477.PA0458; Items: 10 (Box 11)
  - Jimmy Carter, 1976; 6477.PA0459; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Jimmy Carter & Walter Mondale Leaders For A Change, 1976; 6477.PA0460; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - The Majority Of Americans Over 65 Are Vigorous And Capable., 1976; 6477.PA0461; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - For America's Third Century Why Not Our Best?, 1976; 6477.PA0462; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Leaders For A Change, 1976; 6477.PA0463; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Carter-Mondale On the Issues...Acceptance...July 15, 1976, 1976; 6477.PA0464; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Carter-Mondale On the Issues...American Bar Association...August 11, 1976, 1976; 6477.PA0465; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - A Reminder To Construction Workers...The Big Issue Is Jobs, 1976; 6477.PA0466; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Carter VS. Ford, 1976; 6477.PA0467; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Inside: Why Environmental Leaders Hail President Carter's..., ca. 1980; 6477.PA0468; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Ronald Reagan Claims He Isn't An Anti-Labor..., ca. 1980; 6477.PA0469; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Re-Elect President Carter And Vice-President Mondale, 1980; 6477.PA0470; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Take A Few Minutes To Read This Pamphlet!, 1980; 6477.PA0471; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - I Ask The Question Who Is The Architect..., 1980; 6477.PA0472; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Medicare Is Too Important To Turn Over..., 1980; 6477.PA0473; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - At The 1980 Republican Convention The Reaganites Decided..., 1980; 6477.PA0474; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - New York Needs Reagan Bush '84, 1984; 6477.PA0475; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Together '80 Reagan/Bush Team For A New Beginning, 1980; 6477.PA0476; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Reagan Voter Registration Survey Enclosed (Folder), 1984; 6477.PA0477; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Inaugural Items (Schedule, Guidebook, Invitation To Viva '84), 1985; 6477.PA0478; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Official Inaugural Program 1949, 1949; 6477.PA0479; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Presidential Inauguration 1953, 1953; 6477.PA0480; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - 1977 Inaugural Guide To Washington, 1977; 6477.PA0481; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Liz Holtzman Democrat For U.S. Senator, 1980; 6477.PA0482; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Holtzman, Elizabeth
  - E.E. Black For President, n/a; 6477.PA0483; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Candidate: Black, Earl E.
  - Reagan-Bush Commitment '80, 1980; 6477.PA0484; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - If Elected President...Governor Ronald Reagan, 1980; 6477.PA0485; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - On November 4th America Has The Chance To Start Again, 1980; 6477.PA0486; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Why Young America Needs Ronald Reagan For President, 1980; 6477.PA0487; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Time Is Now For An Economic Plan, 1980; 6477.PA0488; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Women's Rights Who Cares?, 1980; 6477.PA0489; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Reagan In Pursuit Of The Presidency-1980, 1980; 6477.PA0490; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Reagan-Bush Newsletter (Vol.1, No.5, October 24, 1980), 1980; 6477.PA0491; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Campaign '80 News New York Tompkins County Republican Committee, 1980; 6477.PA0492; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - A Fighter for the forgotten Middle Class...D'Amato U.S. Senate, 1980; 6477.PA0493; Items: 2 (Box 11)
    Candidate: D'Amato Alfonse
  - For A Positive Change...Neil Wallace For Congress, 1980; 6477.PA0494; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Wallace, Neil
  - Bill Smith Works For You, 1980; 6477.PA0495; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Smith William T.
  - Congressman Gary Lee...Closer To the People, 1980; 6477.PA0496; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - 1980 Political Calendar For Tompkins County, 1980; 6477.PA0497; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - 1980 Facts For Voters...League Of Women Voters Of New York State, 1980; 6477.PA0498; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - League Of Women Voters Of Tompkins County...Voting Guide, 1980; 6477.PA0499; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Neil Wallace Believes In People..., 1980; 6477.PA0500; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - John H. Bartow W.C. Law Judge Republican Candidate..., 1980; 6477.PA0501; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Bartow, John H.
  - What Bryan Could Do...A Menace to Labor And Industry, ca. 1900; 6477.PA0502; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - With Bryan's Consent (Anti-Bryan), ca. 1900; 6477.PA0503; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Consent Of The Governed (Anti-Bryan), ca. 1900; 6477.PA0504; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Sixteen To One...What It Means, 1896; 6477.PA0505; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Election: 1896
  - To The Women Of New York, ca. 1900; 6477.PA0506; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Perils Of Free Silver, ca. 1900; 6477.PA0507; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Sound Money - Sound Business, ca. 1900; 6477.PA0508; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Coal A Barometer Of Prosperity, ca. 1900; 6477.PA0509; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Lincoln 1864--McKinley 1900, 1900; 6477.PA0510; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - From President McKinley's Speech Of Acceptance (In 13 Languages), 1900; 6477.PA0511; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Et Godt Pengesystem Assober...Et Sundt Forretningsliv (German), 1900; 6477.PA0512; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Godt Mynt...Goda Affarer (Swedish), 1900; 6477.PA0513; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - These People Hope You Won't Respond To This Letter..., n/a; 6477.PA0514; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Gary Hart For President Democratic Primary April 3rd, 1984; 6477.PA0515; Items: 2 (Box 11)
  - Only Gary Hart's New Leadership Will Beat Ronald Reagan In November, 1984; 6477.PA0516; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Vote For Gary Hart A New Generation Of Leadership, 1984; 6477.PA0517; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Gary Hart For President (3-page campaign letter), 1984; 6477.PA0518; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Reagan And Students, 1984; 6477.PA0519; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Vote Mondale & Ferraro, 1984; 6744.PA0520; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Citizens Of Tompkins County Your Vote For Mondale And Ferraro..., 1984; 6477.PA0521; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Assemblyman H. Sam MacNeil Reports To The People, 1984; 6477.PA0522; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: MacNeil, H. Sam
  - Make John Currey Assemblyman John Currey, ca. 1984; 6477.PA0523; Items: 1 (Box 11)
    Candidate: Currey, John
  - The Difference Is Like Day And Night, ca. 1984; 6477.PA0524; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - The Jeffersonian June 1932 Convention Issue, 1932; 6477.PA0525; Items: 1 (Box 9)
  - Congressional Record (Issues for May 3, 14 and 17, 1888), 1888; 6477.PA0526; Items: 3 (Box 11)
  - Buffalo Courier Campaign Extra No.2, ca. 1888; 6477.PA0527; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Boston Post Tarrif Reform Extra...August 4 1888, 1888; 6477.PA0528; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - The Labor Signal Supplement, ca. 1888; 6477.PA0529; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Our Bandanna, ca. 1888; 6477.PA0530; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
    Candidate: Harrison, Benjamin
  - Supplement (to unknown newspaper; possibly The Indiana State Sentinel), ca. 1888; 6477.PA0531; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Ognisko (Polish weekly, Nr. 32, Rok II), 1888; 6477.PA0532; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - A Message From Carl McCall, 2002; 6477.PA0533; Items: 1 (Box 11)
  - Tennessee Quarterly, Choosing the President, Cobblestone Magazine, 6477.PA0534; Items: 3 (Box 28)
- Series IX. Paper Miscellaneous
  - "Vote Democratic" Greeting Card, ca. 1956-1992; 6477.PM0001; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Nixon-Lodge Postcard, ca.1960; 6477.PM0002; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - McGovern Postcard, ca. 1972; 6477.PM0003; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Fund-Raising Letter from George McGovern, ca. 1972; 6477.PM0004; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Nixon for President Committee Opinion Survey, ca. 1968; 6477.PM0005; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Republican Party Sustaining Membership Card, 1973, ca. 1973; 6477.PM0006; Items: 5 (Box 7)
  - Coolidge-Dawes Prosperity Special (Imitation Railroad Ticket), ca. 1924; 6477.PM0007; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Coolidge, Calvin
  - Ticket To Andrew Johnson Impeachment April 18, 1868, 1868; 6477.PM0008; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Johnson, Andrew
  - Ticket To Andrew Johnson Impeachment May 11, 1868, 1868; 6477.PM0009; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Joe Talbot Soap Leaf Book and Committee Badge, ca. 1950; 6477.PM0010; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - "I Like Ike" (Postcard with portrait and facsimile signature of Eisenhower), ca. 1952; 6477.PM0011; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - A Prayer That Was Answered (Eisenhower Portrait and Prayer), ca. 1953; 6477.PM0012; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Republican Sincerity/Democratic Insincerity, 1904; 6477.PM0013; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Woodrow Wilson College Men's League Fund-Raising Letter, 1912; 6477.PM0014; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Europe's Warning (Photograph of Battle Scene), ca. 1916; 6477.PM0015; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letter Announcing Wilson Day Calebration, 1916; 6477.PM0016; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letter from Republican Committee Of Tompkins County urging vote, 1916; 6477.PM0017; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Fund-Raising Letter From Charles E. Hughes Big Brother Committee, 1916; 6477.PM0018; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Fund-Raising Letter From National Woodrow Wilson College Men's League, 1916; 6477.PM0019; Items: 5 (Box 7)
  - Hughes National College League Enrollment Materials, 1916; 6477.PM0020; Items: 7 (Box 7)
  - Woodrow Wilson Independent League Letter and Enclosures, 1916; 6477.PM0021; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Postcard Urging Support of Cox and Roosevelt by Independents, 1920; 6477.PM0022; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letter From "Make Hoover President Club", 1920; 6477.PM0023; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letter From The Literary Digest Concerning Sample Primary Ballot, 1920; 6477.PM0024; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Republican National Committee Letter And Questionnaire On Taxation, 1920; 6477.PM0025; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Hoover-For-President Campaign Materials, ca. 1928; 6477.PM0026; Items: 5 (Box 7)
  - Pro-League Independents Letter Confirming Membership, 1920; 6477.PM0027; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Stamps:"1950 The American Way Register And Vote President Truman", 1950; 6477.PM0028; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Letter From Committee For Local Option Signed by Liberty Hyde Bailey, 1918; 6477.PM0029; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letter fFom Citizen Tax-Payers Committee (opposing special election), 1918; 6477.PM0030; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letters From Anti-Saloon League Of New York, 1915; 6477.PM0031; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Home Rule Tax Association Of New York (Letter and enclosures), 1915; 6477.PM0032; Items: 4 (Box 8)
  - Copies of Campaign Letters For Martin H. Glynn; James A. Parsons, 1914; 6477.PM0033; Items: 5 (Box 7)
  - Seabury Non-Partisan Committee Letter And Enrollment Forms, 1916; 6477.PM0034; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Robert Bacon For United States Senator, ca. 1916; 6477.PM0035; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Bacon, Robert
  - How To Vote For Governor X Samuel Seabury, ca. 1916; 6477.PM0036; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Democratic Candidate For State Treasurer Maurice S. Cohen, ca. 1916; 6477.PM0037; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Cohen, Maurice S.
  - Joseph W. Masters... For State Comptroller, ca. 1916; 6477.PM0038; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Republican...Nominee For State Comptroller Eugene M. Travis, ca. 1916; 6477.PM0039; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Travis, Eugene M.
  - Stop The Waste...Get The Barge Canal Done, ca. 1916; 6477.PM0040; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Beebe, Henry R.
  - Frederick W. Palmer Democratic Candidate For Representative..., ca. 1916; 6477.PM0041; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Campaign Letter From Frederick W. Palmer, 1916; 6477.PM0042; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Campaign Materials For Elon H. Hooker, 1920; 6477.PM0043; Items: 3 (Box 8)
    Candidate: Hooker, Elon H.
  - Jim Snyder For Congress, ca. 1982; 6477.PM0044; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Tompkins County Republican Party (Volunteer Packet), 1982; 6477.PM0045; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Matt McHugh For Congress (Family Photo-Postcard), ca. 1982; 6477.PM0046; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Form Letter From Tompkins County Democratic Committee, ca. 1982; 6477.PM0047; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Form Letter From Third Ward (Ithaca) Democratic Committee, 1982; 6477.PM0048; Items: 1 (Box 8)
  - To The Cornell Alumni Of The Sixth Judicial District (Form Letter), 1913; 6477.PM0049; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Sewell, Albert H.
  - Campaign Letter From Fred L. Clock, 1915; 6477.PM0050; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Clock, Fred L.
  - Campaign Letter From Arthur G. Adams, 1915; 6477.PM0051; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Adams, Arthur G.
  - Form Letter and Ticket from National Progressive Party Tompkins County, 1915; 6477.PM0052; Items: 4 (Box 7)
  - Campaign Letter For Tompkins County District Attorney, 1915; 6477.PM0053; Items: 2 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Mintz, Aaron G.
  - Campaign Letter For Tompkins County Treasurer, 1915; 6477.PM0054; Items: 2 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Lent, B. F.
  - Campaign Letter For Justice Of The Supreme Court Sixth Judicial District, 1917; 6477.PM0055; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Sweetland, Monroe M.
    Party: Democratic; Prohibitionist
  - "The Ties Arrived Safe And In Fine Condition" (Postcard signed "Courtney"), 1952; 6477.PM0056; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - "You Are Hereby Appointed Page of the Republican National Convention", 1952; 6477.PM0057; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Courtney Crawford/ Republican National Convention Correspondence, 1952; 6477.PM0058; Items: 12 (Box 7)
  - Courtney Crawford/ Hotel Sherman Materials, 1952; 6477.PM0059; Items: 4 (Box 7)
  - Republican National Convention: Clippings And Miscellaneous Papers, 1952; 6477.PM0060; Items: 4 (Box 7)
  - Republican National Convention: Envelope, Ticket, Press Lounge Pass, 1952; 6477.PM0061; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Letters Pertaining To The Republican National Convention, Chicago, 1952, 1952; 6477.PM0062; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Campaign Letter From Hamilton Fish, 1952; 6477.PM0063; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Fish, Hamilton
  - Tickets To Eisenhower Rally In Madison Square Garden, 1956; 6477.PM0064; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Promotional Material For Book: Revitalizing A Nation...Douglas MacArthur, n/a; 6477.PM0065; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Items Pertaining To New York Republican State Convention, 1954; 6477.PM0066; Items: 5 (Box 7)
  - Elect John L. Joy For Congress, ca. 1964; 6477.PM0067; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Re-Elect To The Assembly...Constance E, Cook Republican, ca. 1964; 6477.PM0068; Items: 3 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Cook, Constance C.
  - Help President Johnson To Continue..., 1964; 6477.PM0069; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - From The Hip...Or From The Head?, 1964; 6477.PM0070; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Young Republicans For Johnson & Keating, 1964; 6477.PM0071; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Re-Elect Ken Keating New York's Own (Postcard), 1964; 6477.PM0072; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - The elephand And The Donkey A Modern Political Fable, 1964; 6477.PM0073; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Social Security?...Straight Talk From Barry Goldwater, 1964; 6477.PM0074; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Ten Reasons Why We should Select Goldwater For President, 1964; 6477.PM0075; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Vote For Barry Goldwater For President Vote Republican, 1964; 6477.PM0076; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - A Personal Note: Victory Is In The Air! (Campaign Letter), 1964; 6477.PM0077; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - A Vote For Francis J. Souhan Is A vote To end "Taberism" (Card), ca. 1960; 6477.PM0078; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Hold The Fort (Poem For Tilden by "J.H."), ca. 1876; 6477.PM0079; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Tilden, Samuel J.
    Election: 1876
  - Anti-Reagan Postcards (From One World Artist Cooperative), 1982; 6477.PM0080; Items: 9 (Box 7)
  - Portrait of Louis J. Lefkowitz (Postcards), ca. 1970; 6477.PM0081; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Happy Rockefeller's Coffee Cake (Recipe Cards), ca. 1970; 6477.PM0082; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Young New Yorkers For Rockefeller (Membership Forms), ca. 1970; 6477.PM0083; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Independents For Rockefeller (Cards From Canvasser's Kit), ca. 1970; 6477.PM0084; Items: 4 (Box 7)
  - Vote for the Senator (Labor Committee for Javits), ca. 1968; 6477.PM0085; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Hubert H. Humphrey (Photo & signature; N.Y. Giants schedule on verso), ca. 1968; 6477.PM0086; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Invest One Dollar For Peace (Booklet of McCarthy Coupons), ca. 1968; 6477.PM0087; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - For An Open Convention (Survey and Pledge Postcard), ca. 1968; 6477.PM0088; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - "Come...Let Us Reason Together" (Postcard/ Portrait of LBJ), ca. 1964; 6477.PM0089; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Admission Tickets to Republican National Convention, Cleveland, 1924, 1924; 6477.PM0090; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - McHugh For Congress (Postcard: Family Photograph), ca. 1976; 6477.PM0091; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Welch for Congress, ca. 1976; 6477.PM0092; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Welch, Charles
  - Gary Lee, ca. 1976; 6477.PM0093; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Tom Loll For State Senator, ca. 1976; 6477.PM0094; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Loll, Tom
  - Siegel For State Senate, ca. 1980; 6477.PM0095; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Re-Admit Tickets For Republican National Convention July 1980, 1980; 6477.PM0096; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Card Of Appreciation For Contributions By Jim Ray, ca. 1984; 6477.PM0097; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Your Key To A Voice In Washington, n/a; 6477.PM0098; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Reed, Delores M.
  - Postcard & Letter Promoting William C. Barrett For Tompkins County Judge, 1980; 6477.PM0099; Items: 2 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Barrett, William C.
  - Campaign Letter Promoting John H. Bartow For Tompkins County Judge, ca. 1980; 6477.PM0100; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Presidential Inaugural Committee - 1985 (News Releases), 1984; 6477.PM0101; Items: 19 (Box 8)
  - 50th American Presidential Inaugural Commemoratives 1985 (Catalogue), 1985; 6477.PM0102; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Invitation To 50th...Inaugural With Accompanying Explanatory Card, 1985; 6477.PM0103; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - Why Be A Republican? (Card From N.Y. Republican State Committee), n/a; 6477.PM0104; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letters To The Editor From Mrs. Charlotte D. Fultz (Newspaper Clippings), 1993; 1994; 6477.PM0105; Items: 4 (Box 7)
  - Matt McHugh For Congress (Family Photo-Postcard: Differs From PM0047), ca. 1984; 6477.PM0106; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Albert Gore Family Photograph/ Christmas Card (Dated Dec. '95), 1995; 6477.PM0107; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Invitation From President Reagan To Help Sponsor The GOP Victory Fund, ca. 1984; 6477.PM0108; Items: 3 (Box 7)
  - Health Care Reform Task Force Fund-Raising Letter (Anti-Clinton), ca. 1996; 6477.PM0109; Items: 2 (Box 7)
  - National Conservative Club Fund-Raising Letter (Anti-Clinton), 1996; 6477.PM0110; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Republican National Commission On the American Agenda (Two Surveys), ca. 1994; 6477.PM0111; Items: 2 (Box 7)
    Election: 1994
  - Postcard To Hon. Newt Gingrich From Mrs. C.D. Futz (Carbon copy), ca. 1995; 6477.PM0112; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Letter To President Bill Clinton From Mrs. C.D. Futz, 1994; 6477.PM0113; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - The Democratic National Committee's Campaign To Recapture...(Calendar), 1986; 6477.PM0114; Items: 1 (Box 7)
  - Membership Certificate Republican League Of The United States, 1888; 6477.PM0115; Items: 1 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Photostats of fragile Broadsides 6477.BR0255 thru 6477.BR0267, various; 6477.PM0116; Items: 26 (Mapcase-folder X-24)
  - Governor George Pataki...Leadership That Works, ca. 2002; 6477.PM0117; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Pataki, George
  - Gail Hilson For State Assembly, ca. 2002; 6477.PM0118; Items: 1 (Box 7)
    Candidate: Hilson, Gail
  - World's Smallest Political Quiz, 2004; 6477.PM0119; Items: 2 (Box 27)
  - Resist! newspaper, 2016; Items: 1 (Box 17)
    Election: 2016
    Candidate: Donald Trump
  - NY Daily News, 2016-08-10; Items: 1 (Box 17)
  - Generation of Peace stamps, 1972; 6477.PM0120; Items: 1 sheet (Box 27)
  - Million Dollar Bill, 6477.PM0121; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Election: 1993
  - 2004 Presidential Debates packet: pamphlet, 2004; 6477.PM0122; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Kerry, John
  - 2004 Presidential Debates packet: special guest pass, 2004; 6477.PM0123; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - 2004 Presidential Debates packet: parking pass, 2004; 6477.PM0124; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - 2004 Presidential Debates packet: Food for Debate card, 2004; 6477.PM0125; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - On Tuesday, we're voting our values,", 2006; 6477.PM0126; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Arcuri, Mike
    Election: 2006
    Party: Working Families
  - Leaders, for a change, 1984; 6477.PM0127; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "She has no plans to let up on Bush,", 2006; 6477.PM0128; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Clinton, Hillary
  - "He took on the NRA...,", 2006; 6477.PM0129; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Cuomo, Andrew
  - New York Democrats have taken measurements...,", 2006; 6477.PM0130; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "Eliot Spitzer is leaving some very big shoes to fill,", 2007; 6477.PM0131; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - Danby [NY] Democratic Committee slate of candidates, 2006; 6477.PM0132; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Dietrich, Ric
    Candidate: Strichartz, Naomi
    Candidate: Gagnon, Joel
    Candidate: Szcepanski, Carol
    Candidate: Catlin, Gerald, Jr.
    Candidate: Thurnheer, Andrew
  - Green letter to Dems and the GOP, 9/16/2003 [2 pp.], 2003; 6477.PM0133; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Glover, Paul
    Election: 2003
  - Green Giant, 8/6/2003 article, 2003; 6477.PM0134; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - Mayoral forum article, 10/7/2003 [2 pp.], 2003; 6477.PM0135; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Petersen, Carolyn
    Candidate: Saul, John Beau
  - Ithaca mayoral candidates article, 10/20/2003 [2 pp.], 2003; 6477.PM0136; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - Leading the way, 10/29/2003 [1 p. orignal, 2 pp. photocopy], 2003; 6477.PM0137; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - The Future of Ithaca, 10/29/2003 [2 pp.], 2003; 6477.PM0138; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "Send a message on Tuesday...,", 2007; 6477.PM0139; Items: 1 (Box 27)
    Candidate: Lifton, Barbara
    Election: 2007
  - "Assemblywoman Barbara Lifton, Improving women's lives...,", 2006; 6477.PM0140; Items: 1 (Box 27)
  - "Assemblywoman Barbara Lifton wants to meet with you,", 2007; 6477.PM0141; Items: 1 (Box 27)